abstrusegoose.com 2012-12-21

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

* * *

Abstruse Goose ("AG" or "we") uses third party advertising networks to serve ads to visitors of the AG website. These companies may use information about your visit in order to provide relevant advertisements that may be of interest to you. AG currently uses the following advertising networks . We recommend that you review their individual privacy statements (links included): 

  * **Google AdSense** : Google uses cookies - including the DoubleClick DART cookie - when displaying ads on web pages. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on the internet sites you visit, enabling it to serve ads that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). You can read the Privacy Policy for Google ads [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html).

* * *

AG uses third-party analytics services to collect statistics about how visitors interact with the website. Under no circumstances will AG use the analytics tools to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information of visitors to the site. AG currently uses the following analytics services. We encourage you to review their individual privacy statements (links included):

  * **Google Analytics** : Google Analytics uses cookies to track visitor interactions. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. You can read Google's Privacy Policy [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/privacy-policy.html).

* * *

AG respects, and is committed to, the privacy of website visitors. As part of that commitment, AG provides this policy statement to provide transparency in privacy-related matters. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement, please contact us at this email address.

Last updated on December 18, 2012.
